Guide to the George and Louise Spindler Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
George and Louise Spindler papers
1947-1991
SC0493
Spindler, George Dearborn.
Spindler, Louise S.
30 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of George and Louise Spindler, 1995.
Biographical/Historical note
George Spindler joined the Stanford faculty in 1950, as professor of anthropology and education. Louise Spindler earned the first Ph.D. in anthropology awarded by Stanford in 1956 and remained with the department as lecturer and research associate. They retired in 1978, but continued to teach occasional classes.
Scope and Contents note
Professional papers of George and Louise Spindler pertaining to their research, publications, courses taught, and departmental matters; papers include correspondence, memoranda, articles, course materials, case studies, research proposals, and photographs. Their research interests included the Menominee Indians of Wisconsin, the Blood and Cree Indians of Canada, ethnography of schooling, and urbanizing villages in Germany.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Department of Anthropology. Faculty.; Anthropology--Study and teaching.; Cree Indians.; Educational anthropology.; Indians of North America.; Kainah Indians.; Menominee Indians.; Urbanization--Germany.
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Shimahara, Nobuo, 1967 November 10-1971 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Simirenko, Alex, 1968 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Not To Be Published, 1966 February 16-1974 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barrett, Richard, 1970 May 20-1973 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bascom, William, 1960 November 8-1973 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Basso, Ellen, 1970 January 23-1972 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Basso, Keith, 1967 September 4-1969 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beals, Alan, 1962 February 12-1963 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beattie, John, 1959 October 23-1973 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Beattie, John, 1964 February 27-1965 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Benet, Sula, 1970 May 21-1973 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Boissevan, Jeremy, 1964 June 24-1971 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Brim, John, 1970 October 6-1974 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Buechler, Hans C., 1968 March 22-1971 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chagnon, Napoleon A., 1966 December 4-1970 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chagnon, Napoleon - Methods Study, 1967 December 5-1973 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chance, Norman, 1960 December 1-1967 February 4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chinas, Beverly, 1970 February 15-1972 July 17 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Ronald, 1965 February 15-1969 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cohen, Ronald, 1966 January 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Collier, John, 1970 July 16-1971 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Collier, John, Jr., 1964 December 8-1968 August 23 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Davidson, Ted, 1971 March 11-1975 July 10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Deng, Francis, 1969 June 6-1974 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dentan, R.K., Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dentan, R.K., 1966 March 5-1968 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Diamond, Norma, 1964 December 14-1969 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Downs, James, 1964 March 13-1966 December 23 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Downs, James F. - The Navajo, 1962 April 16-1970 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dozier, Edward P. - The Kalinga, 1966 January 19-September 26 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dozier, Edward P., 1963 December 15-1966 January 4 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dozier, Edward, 1967 October 27-1969 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dunn, Stephen, 1964 September 1-1974 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dunn, Stephen P., Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Ekvall, Robert B., 1965 January 5-1968 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fakhouri, Hani, 1970 May 11-1971 October 5 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fraser, Thomas M., Jr., 1964 March 25-1966 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Friedl, Ernestine, 1961 May 3-1962 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Friedl, John, 1971 September 14-1974 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Friedland, William, 1970 February 17-1972 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Furer-Haimendorf, C. Von, 1966 November 27-1968 November 6 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gabel, Creighton, 1965 March 9-1966 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gamst, Frederick, 1967 June 12-1974 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Garbarino, M.S., 1969 November 17-1975 August 4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Gay, John, 1965 November 1-1969 March 18 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Grindal, Bruce, 1969 September 16-1972 January 31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gudschinsky, Sarah C., 1965 February 21-1967 June 7 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Halpern, Joel M., 1962 January 10-1971 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Clement, 1971 November 4-1972 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Henry, Frances, 1966 January 6-1969 April 24 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hickerson, Harold, 1965 May 6-1970 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hitchcock, John, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hitchcock, John, 1964 January 1-1966 September 22 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hogbin, Ian, 1963 March 4-October 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Holmes, Lowell, 1968 January 4-1973 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Horowitz, Michael M., 1964 March 5-1966 November 27 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hostetler, John A., 1965 January 26-1966 November 29 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hostetler, 1966 October 27-1971 April 22 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hsu, Francis L.K., 1967 July 17-1969 April 10 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hudson, Alfred, 1967 May 19-1972 January 6 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Jacobs, Jerry, 1971 August 6-1974 April 5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jocano, F. Landa, 1967 January 19-1969 March 11 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jones, David, 1970 January 6-1971 June 4 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kearney, Michael, 1971 March 18-September 21 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Keesing, Roger, 1957 April 8-1971 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kiefer, Thomas, 1969 October 1-1975 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - King, A. Richard, 1965 June 10-1969 February 26 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Klima, George, 1966 July 8-1973 December 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kunkel, Peter, 1967 October 14-1971 November 5 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kuper, Hilda, 1960 November 28-1963 August 23 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Leis, Philip, 1967 May 31-1971 December 21 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lessa, William A., 1963 December 2-1966 March 4 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Madsen, William, 1963 January 15-1973 February 12 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mcfee, Malcolm, 1969 December 29-1971 June 18 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Messenger, John, 1962 February 15-1974 November 12 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Middleton, John, 1961 August 25-1972 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Middleton, John (M), 1966 September 10-1971 June 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Modiano, Nancy, 1967 December 6-1972 November 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Ohnuki-Tierney, 1971 January 14-1973 September 11 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Opler, Morris, 1961 February 15-1969 August 14 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - O'Toole, 1970 August 1-1974 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Partridge, William, 1970 April 24-1972 November 15 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pilcher, William, 1971 April 29-1972 February 24 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Peshkin, Alan, 1970 January 16-1975 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pierce, Joe E., 1963 April 26-1965 December 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1963 December 9-1966 June 10 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Pi-Sunyer, Oriol, 1969 December 29-1973 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pitt, David, 1968 January 6-1974 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Norbeck, 1972 November 25 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pitt-Rivers, Julian, 1958 January 23-1961 April 7 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pospisil, Leopold, 1961 September 22-1963 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Quintana, Berta, 1970 April 21-1975 August 4 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Read, Margaret, 1966 April 15-1967 October 3 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Richardson, Miles, 1967 September 9-1973 December 26 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Riviere, 1969 April 29-1971 December 9 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Rohner, Ronald, 1966 October 21-1972 March 23 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Rosenfeld, Gerry, 1968 December 3-1971 June 18 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rubin, Morton, 1970 March 4-1974 January 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Safa, Helen, 1969 June 6-1973 April 22 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Salzman, Zdenek, 1969 February 17-1973 November 28 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Schusky, Ernest L., 1961 June 20-1969 January 17 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Schusky, Ernest L., 1968 October 8 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Schusky, 1969 May 20-1971 October 8 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Singleton, John, 1964 November 5-1967 March 9 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Spindler, 1970 April 13-1974 January 31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Spindler, 1971 May 4-1973 October 15 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Thomas, Murray, 1967 November 15-1968 August 30 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1969 June 28-July 8 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Thompson, Laura, 1969 January 3-1970 October 20 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Torres-Trueba, 1971 December 2-1972 March 29 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Trigger, 1969 July 23 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Turnbull, Colin, 1972 May 18-June 21 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Turner, Paul, 1972 June 20-1974 August 7 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Tway, Patricia, 1974 July 19-1975 July 30 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Tweddell, Colin, 1968 April 1-May 8 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Tyrner-Stastny, 1972 December 7-1973 April 4 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - van den Berghe, Pierre, 1966 October 5-1974 October 16 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Voget, Fred W., 1965 December 13-1975 January 6 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Wagley, Charles, 1964 December 1-1975 March 24 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Wagner, Roy, 1966 May 18-June 13 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Watson, James, 1973 October 3-1975 March 24 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - White, Doug, 1970 July 1-1972 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Whiting, John, 1964 November 12-1966 March 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Whitten, Norman E., 1968 April 15-November 12 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Winther, Paul, 1972 October 18-November 14 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Wodinsky, Carol, 1969 October 20-1970 January 9 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Wood, W. Raymond, 1970 August 17-September 30 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dead File more or less CSCA, 1967 May 26-1969 October 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Untitled, 1968 June 10-11 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Recent Correspondence, 1968 September 21-1969 October 11 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Case Studies - Approach Again?, 1972 January 12-28 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Abler, Thomas, 1970 June 15 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Appell, George, 1968 June 22-1969 July 22 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Archer, Dale, 1968 July 16-1969 June 3 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Arewa, E. Ojo, 1967 February 15-April 27 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Arvizu, Campbell, 1970 June 28-1972 July 19 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ashcraft, Norman, 1970 October 21-November 30 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Austin, 1970 January 19-March 30 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Bailey, Garrick, 1970 June 24-July 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Barth, Frederik, 1966 November 22-December 28 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Bean, Lowell J., 1970 August 24-1972 April 10 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Bennett, John W., 1966 January 11-March 9 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Bernard, H. Russell, 1967 December 12-1968 March 17 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Berndt, Ronald, 1968 March 17 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Berreman, Gerald, 1962 November 30-1965 December 2 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Bestor, William, 1972 August 21-October 4 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Biebuyck, Daniel, 1967 July 14-September 21 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Black, Mary, 1966 December 28-1974 September 9 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Block, Harriet, 1973 June 26-1974 March 27 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bolton, Ralph, 1969 December 6-1972 October 4 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Brain, Robert, 1967 April 4 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Briggs, Jean, 1970 November 30-1971 January 8 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Buckley, D.L., 1972 April 5-1974 February 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Carmack, Robert, 1971 March 2-November 9 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cernea, 1972 July 28 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Chaney, Richard, 1971 May 14-November 9 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Chiao, Chien, 1970 May 7-August 19 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Myron, 1968 March 4-September 10 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Collins, June, 1969 December 4-1970 April 9 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Colson, A., Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Comitas, Lambros, 1966 December 1-19 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - d'Azevedo, 1968 January 23-1972 December 16 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Deetz, 1970 January 2-1975 June 17 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Deng, Francis, 1973 December 10-1974 January 7 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dennis, Benjamin, 1966 September 29-1968 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dentan, 1969 April 23-May 4 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Dougherty, Molly C., 1970 June 18-1974 October 14 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Douglass, William, 1966 June 13-September 8 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Dowling, John, 1970 February 23-1973 October 16 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Drews, Robin, 1969 August 15-September 3 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Dyson-Hudson, Neville, 1965 January 5-December 28 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Eggan, Fred, 1966 March 18-1968 January 22 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Evans-Pritchard, E.E., 1957 January 29-1965 May 17 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Fabrega, Horatio, Jr., 1970 November 16-December 29 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Faron, L.C., 1968 January 17 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Fetz, Jennifer, 1971 July 22-August 6 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Foley, Douglas, 1972 September 20-1973 March 20 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - French, Robt. Mills, 1970 November 19-1971 March 4 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Friedl, Ernestine, 1966 May 2-1974 September 16 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Gale, Charlotte, 1969 May 26 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Garfield, 1962 November 30-1967 January 19 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Geertz, 1962 November 30-1966 April 22 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Gelfand, May E., 1966 October 13-26 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Gonzales, N., 1971 May 5-September 21 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Graves, Theodore, 1969 November 12-December 2 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Greenway, John, 1968 March 14-1971 February 2 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Griffith, Pearson, 1971 August 18-1972 November 10 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Gross, Daniel, 1972 January 6-March 30 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Gross, Feliks, 1969 August 20-December 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hagopian, Elaine C., 1963 August 13-1966 May 13 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hall, 1965 November 24-December 22 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hallowell, 1962 September 22-1969 March 25 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Halpern, 1971 December 11-1972 February 24 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hammel, E.A., 1966 March 30-1968 December 9 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hammond, Philip, 1970 April 20-1972 November 15 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Hanifi, 1970 September 21-1972 March 28 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Harding, Thomas, 1968 September 10-1970 January 13 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Harkins, 1969 September 18-1970 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Harman, Robert, 1971 November 5-1972 December 15 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hatch, Elwin, 1969 November 23-1970 March 12 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Heath, 1962 December 5-1968 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Hickman, Pollnac, 1972 November 18-1973 January 19 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Hicks, David, 1969 November 28-1974 August 20 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Hill, Carole, 1973 February 22-October 17 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Hitchcock, John, 1967 May 1-26 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Hitchcock, John T., 1966 March 29-April 26 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Hodge, William, 1969 July 18-1972 June 2 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Hole, Frank, 1969 January 5-1970 February 16 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Holloman, Regina, 1969 July 31-October 18 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Holmes, Lowell, 1973 August 27-1974 April 10 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Honigman, John J., 1965 December 7-1968 October 9 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Hudson, Charles, 1970 October 2-1972 August 20 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Hughes, Charles C., 1966 January 11-February 4 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Irons, William, 1967 December 11-1972 July 31 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Islam, A.K.M. Aminul, 1967 June 9-1972 March 30 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Jacobson, David, 1970 September 23-November 20 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Jaspan, M.A., 1965 March 30-April 21 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Jennings, Jesse, 1970 February 16-July 1 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Johnson, Colleen, 1973 March 26 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Jones, Richard, 1970 February 23-1972 April 11 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Jones, Schuyler, 1968 January 24-1969 October 3 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Kertzer, David, 1974 January 11-September 3 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Khera, Sigrid, 1971 September 17-1972 January 3 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Kiste, Robert, 1970 July 15-October 7 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Kite, Herb, 1972 May 24 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Kloos, Peter, 1970 May 26-July 14 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Krader, Lawrence, 1964 December 14-1965 April 17 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Kuper, Hilda, 1968 May 6-1970 February 24 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Kurtz, Ronald J., 1965 July 5-November 4 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Lancaster, 1970 December 1-1974 August 15 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Lancaster, Will, 1974 January 11-June 4 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Langman, Lauren, 1972 April 25-September 11 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Lex, Barbara, 1971 October 15-1974 April 16 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Lienhardt, 1963 October 17-1967 May 19 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lutfiyya, Abdulla, 1968 December 22-1970 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Machold, Ilse, 1970 December 22-1971 November 29 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Magnorella, Paul, 1972 March 30-October 11 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Maloney, Thomas, 1970 March 30-1973 February 9 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Manners, Robert, 1970 May 12-1971 January 8 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Marwick, M.G., 1965 July 19-1966 January 28 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Mason, Len, 1971 February 11-April 16 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Mayer, Philip, 1963 April 3-1967 June 25 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Medlin, William, 1966 March 7-1969 February 27 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Meggitt, Mervyn, 1964 December 14-1965 April 5 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell, William, 1973 April 20-1975 June 18 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Molony, Carol, 1971 September 28-1975 May 19 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Morgan, Gordon, 1970 September 22-1974 May 2 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Myerhoff, Barbara, 1974 February 27-November 12 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Myers, James, 1970 August 13-1971 September 21 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Nader, Laura, 1965 January 2-1971 February 3 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Nayacakatou, R.R., 1966 September 19 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Nimmo, Arlo, 1967 August 31-1969 April 11 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Nurge, Ethel, 1970 October 1-1973 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Nutting, 1969 April 7-30 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Ohuche, R. Ogbonna, 1969 March 21-October 22 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Okediji, Oladejo, 1967 December 15-1968 May 9 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Oosterwal, Gottfried, 1971 November 8-1972 June 12 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Oswalt, 1969 May 5-1970 October 22 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Paine, Robert, 1969 December 11-1970 February 9 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Pearson, Keith, 1969 December 3-1971 January 12 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Pitt, David, 1970 August 6-1975 January 6 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Poggie, John, 1970 April 29-July 24 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Press, Irwin, 1970 August 10-1973 November 20 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Provencher, Ronald, 1969 November 27-December 29 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Provinzano, James, 1971 August 19-September 21 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Rajput, 1970 March 20-June 8 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Randolph, Richard R., 1964 January 1-1970 February 6 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Redekop, Calvin, 1963 May 4-1970 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Regestreif, Donna, 1971 February 2-1972 March 28 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Renato, Shelly, 1971 June 22 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Rohner, 1968 November 1-1970 November 20 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Rosenstiel, Annette, 1966 April 14-26 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Sable, Joseph Alan, 1966 January 11-1974 September 9 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Salisbury, Lee H., 1966 September 26-November 16 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Salzman, Philip C., 1967 March 29-1971 November 10 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Sapaula, Crispina C., 1966 March 23-June 6 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sapin, David, 1968 April 15-1970 November 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Savishinsky, Joel, 1971 January 5-September 15 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Scheffler, 1963 April 7-September 13 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Schlegel, Stuart, 1970 February 4-April 23 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Schneider, Harold, 1968 July 8 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Schulman, Sam, 1968 March 4-1970 August 3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Schwarz, Henry, 1972 March 17-1973 October 26 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Shavinshinsky, Joel, 1970 October 15-November 20 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Sherzer, Joel, 1970 January 7-March 17 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Silverman, Sydel, 1969 May 19-July 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sindell, Peter, 1967 September 9-1970 August 28 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Slater, Mariam, 1966 May 13-24 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Alfred G., 1958 July 22-1969 April 30 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Sorenson, Richard, 1970 February 20-1971 May 4 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sutherland, Ann, 1972 March 25-1973 January 19 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Swett, Daniel, 1968 November 26-1969 May 21 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Untitled, 1953 December 14 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Sugarman, Barry, 1969 July 4-1973 August 15 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Being an Anthropologist, 1968 September 3-1970 October 8 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, Carol, 1967 June 5 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Trigger, Bruce, 1966 December 1-1970 September 22 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Trigger, Bruce G., 1965 March 18-1969 July 18 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Turner, Paul, 1969 May 16-1971 September 23 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Uchendu, Victor, 1963 May 1-1964 December 16 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Vogt, Evon Z., 1960 November 2-1971 November 3 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ward, Martha, 1970 January 14-October 7 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Warren, Richard A., 1966 March 15-1967 May 24 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Thomas R., 1966 March 16-1971 July 21 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Williams, Thomas Rhys, 1964 December 11-1966 October 6 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Thomas R. (affair), 1962 November 29-1966 July 28 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Thomas Rhys, 1959 December 7-1966 December 8 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Williams, Thomas R., 1964 November 30-1969 October 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Wolcott, Harry, 1964 December 9-1967 June 23 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Wolcott, Harry, 1970 July 10-1972 November 14 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NSF, 1969 May 31-1970 August 31 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Education-Financial, 1958 October 2-1971 September 7 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Education Dept.-General, 1967 February 27-1974 August 26 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cultural Pluralism, 1973 March 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ayabe, Tsuneo, 1967 February 9-1968 July 20 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Baty, Roger, 1968 October 17 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Cummings, Steve, 1970 March 5-6 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Foley, Douglas, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Fruehling, Royal, 1966 September 27-1969 January 9 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hamilton, Bruce, 1969 May 19 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Kline, Bill, 1969 May 12-15 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lueders, Erika, 1969 April 9-June 5 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Fishburn, 1967 May 29-1969 May 20 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rodriguez, Sylvia, 1973 July 26 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - White, John, 1972 March 14-1973 March 28 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Anthro-Education, 1970 November 17-1974 April 26 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Anthro. Dept.-General, 1974 October 14-1975 August 4 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Anthro. Dept-Recommendations, 1975 May 15-July 9 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Anthro. Dept.-General, 1971 January 2-1975 May 7 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations-Anthro, 1969 September 3-1975 March 17 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Recommendations-Stanford-general, 1970 December 18-1974 March 16 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Advising-General, 1972 May 22-September 14 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Major Advisees, 1969 February 26 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Teaching Schedule, 1968 December 30-1974 April 15 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Anthro Graduate Program, 1969 May 13-1973 March 21 (Box 16, Folder 19)